[
    {
      "question": "There are 5 core Lasallian values. Which of these is NOT one of them?",
      "choice1": "Commitment to Honesty and Integrity",
      "choice2": "Quality Education",
      "choice3": "Concern for the Poor, and Social Justice",
      "choice4": "Faith in the Presence of God",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the founder of the De La Salle Christian Brothers and the values they represent?",
      "choice1": "Frederick LaSalle",
      "choice2": "John Baptiste de La Salle",
      "choice3": "Jeffrey Baptiste de La Salle",
      "choice4": "Mary Augustine de La Salle",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What demographic were the Brothers' especially commited to upon their founding?",
      "choice1": "Girls",
      "choice2": "Christians",
      "choice3": "The unfaithful",
      "choice4": "The Poor",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Lasallian tradition and values are rooted in which Christian tradition?",
        "choice1": "Baptist",
        "choice2": "Lutheran",
        "choice3": "Evangelical",
        "choice4": "Catholic",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Lasallian colleges and Universities are in the United States as of 2023?",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "13",
        "choice3": "6",
        "choice4": "4",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country was the De La Salle Christian Brothers first founded?",
        "choice1": "France",
        "choice2": "Italy",
        "choice3": "Germany",
        "choice4": "Spain",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In which century was the institution of the De La Salle Brothers founded?",
        "choice1": "18th Century",
        "choice2": "17th Century",
        "choice3": "19th Century",
        "choice4": "16th Century",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What title was given to the founder of the De La Salle Christian Brothers?",
        "choice1": "God's Teacher",
        "choice2": "The Catholic Mentor",
        "choice3": "The Patron Saint of Teachers",
        "choice4": "The Scholarly Saint",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is not one of the core values of Lasallian schools?",
        "choice1": "Individualistic Excellence",
        "choice2": "Help the disadvantaged and poor",
        "choice3": "Foster a community where student's and teacher's help each other",
        "choice4": "Support and advocate for service through education",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How does one become a Lasallian Brother?",
        "choice1": "Attend an annual retreat with other Brothers, and 5 to 8 years of profession and vows",
        "choice2": "Become baptized by a Brother and commit to a year of vows",
        "choice3": "Retreat to a year of living with the Brothers",
        "choice4": "Apply at a Lasallian School",
        "answer": 1
    }
]